{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316602601","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316602600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HELIKOPTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316607296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316607295"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HELIKOPTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316608850","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316608849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUFU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316612618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316612618"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUFU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316614207","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316614206"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUJAMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316618627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316618626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUJAMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316620256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316620256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316625324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316625324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316626908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316626908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUSI"," userResponse":" HARUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316632729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316632729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316634293","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316634293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOSPITALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316638568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316638568"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOSPITALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316640134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316640134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUNYWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316643604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316643604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUNYWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316645166","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316645166"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" HOHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316648519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316648518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316650078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316650078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HEMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEMA"," userResponse":" HEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316653124","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316653124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HEMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316654684","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316654684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" HASIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316658654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316658654"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316660667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316660667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316660795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316660794"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316671162","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316671162"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" ddd1cc5a-4988-4cac-bfea-f8262cff8a46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316682687","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316682687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HELIKOPTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316690884","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316690884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HELIKOPTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316692470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316692470"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUFU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316696576","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316696576"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUFU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316698148","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316698147"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUJAMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316702881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316702881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUJAMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316704446","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316704445"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316708458","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316708457"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316710047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316710047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUSI"," userResponse":" HARUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316714217","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316714217"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316715792","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316715792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOSPITALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316720788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316720788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOSPITALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316722373","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316722373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUNYWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316727871","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316727871"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUNYWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316729428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316729428"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" HOHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316732787","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316732787"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316734345","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316734345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HEMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEMA"," userResponse":" HEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316737415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316737415"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HEMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316738983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316738983"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" HASIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316742666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316742665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316744693","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316744693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316744936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316744936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316753134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316753133"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 430a1bc2-0714-4428-b7c2-bf8c1f2ef58e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316763651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316763651"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a8a0c220-b60a-4bd5-8bf4-1abb03b990a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_Y-H-W"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316768223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316768223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a8a0c220-b60a-4bd5-8bf4-1abb03b990a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-CH-K"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316771501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316771501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a8a0c220-b60a-4bd5-8bf4-1abb03b990a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_F-M-H"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316777298","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316777297"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a8a0c220-b60a-4bd5-8bf4-1abb03b990a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_F-M-H"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316808953","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316808952"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a8a0c220-b60a-4bd5-8bf4-1abb03b990a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_I-H-F"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316814537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316814537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a8a0c220-b60a-4bd5-8bf4-1abb03b990a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-W-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316835067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316835066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a8a0c220-b60a-4bd5-8bf4-1abb03b990a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-E-N"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316840670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316840670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a8a0c220-b60a-4bd5-8bf4-1abb03b990a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-S-F"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316845567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316845567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a8a0c220-b60a-4bd5-8bf4-1abb03b990a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_O-H-N"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316849487","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316849487"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a8a0c220-b60a-4bd5-8bf4-1abb03b990a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_S-R-H"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316853263","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316853263"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a8a0c220-b60a-4bd5-8bf4-1abb03b990a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-E-M"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316859028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316859028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a8a0c220-b60a-4bd5-8bf4-1abb03b990a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-E-M"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316871040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316871040"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a8a0c220-b60a-4bd5-8bf4-1abb03b990a8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-E-M"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316881417","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316881416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316881814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316881814"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316882303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316882302"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316882657","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316882657"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316883062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316883062"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316883551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316883551"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316883785","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316883782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316887002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316887002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316887036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316887036"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316887754","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316887754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316888156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316888155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316888456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316888456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316888667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316888667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316888872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316888872"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316889194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316889193"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316889429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316889428"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316892659","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316892658"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316893070","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316893069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316895626","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316895626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316895843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316895842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316896056","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316896056"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316899587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316899587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316903337","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316903337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316904377","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316904377"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316907058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316907057"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316907441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316907441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316907933","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316907933"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316908281","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316908280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316908691","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316908690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316909175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316909174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316909404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316909403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316912654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316912654"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316912693","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316912693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316913412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316913411"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316913811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316913811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316914109","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316914108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316914320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316914319"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316914532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316914532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316914853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316914853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316915081","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316915081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316917672","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316917672"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316917771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316917771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 80da46e3-2748-4baf-8c1f-90069e8426c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316927802","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316927802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316928313","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316928313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316929459","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316929459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316932295","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316932295"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316933021","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316933021"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316933605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316933604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316936420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316936420"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316937116","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316937116"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316937652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316937652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316937868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316937868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316938727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316938726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316941486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316941486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316942030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316942029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316943076","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316943076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316945808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316945807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316946531","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316946530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316947110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316947110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316949987","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316949987"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316950701","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316950701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316951190","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316951189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316951400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316951399"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316952090","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316952090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316955423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316955422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316956054","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316956053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316957703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316957702"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPALILIA"," userResponse":" ALIPALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316958503","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316958503"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316959048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316959047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316959687","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316959687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316962448","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316962448"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316962927","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316962927"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316964646","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316964646"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYUNYIZIA"," userResponse":" ALINYUNYIZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316965404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316965404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316965946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316965946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316966532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316966532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316969471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316969471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316969745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316969744"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316970456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316970456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316971289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316971289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316971989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316971989"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFANYA"," userResponse":" TULIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316972576","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316972572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316973310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316973310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316974065","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316974065"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316974529","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316974529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZO"," userResponse":" HIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316975064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316975064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316977484","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316977483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316977777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316977777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316978321","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316978321"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316979264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316979264"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316979828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316979828"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIVUNA"," userResponse":" TULIVUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316980542","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316980542"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316980855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316980855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316981739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316981739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316985024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316985024"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316985538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316985538"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316985762","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316985762"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316986656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316986656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316987589","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316987588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIZAA"," userResponse":" ILIZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316988585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316988584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGUNIA"," userResponse":" MAGUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316988795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316988795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316989665","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316989665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316992253","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316992253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316992765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316992765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316992968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316992967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316993632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316993632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316994656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316994656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIZAA"," userResponse":" ILIZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316995655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316995655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGUNIA"," userResponse":" MAGUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316995938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316995938"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316996644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316996643"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316999471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316999471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316999982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316999982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317001142","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317001142"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317004101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317004101"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317004830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317004829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317005471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317005471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317007953","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317007952"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317008554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317008554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317009824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317009824"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYOPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIYOPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317010676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317010676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317010929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317010929"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317011799","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317011798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317014745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317014745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317015285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317015285"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317016344","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317016343"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317019212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317019212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317019947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317019947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317020582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317020582"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317023165","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317023165"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317023729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317023729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317024951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317024951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYOPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIYOPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317025784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317025784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317026029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317026028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317026744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317026744"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317029461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317029457"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317029570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317029570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0874c3ff-ac5d-44c1-9453-4474dda368ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317039928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317039928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a45b65e6-0e84-4fa3-a596-7b35eb38fb2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-J-B"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317047335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317047334"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a45b65e6-0e84-4fa3-a596-7b35eb38fb2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_Y-G-H"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317051331","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317051331"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a45b65e6-0e84-4fa3-a596-7b35eb38fb2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-R-L"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317054466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317054466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a45b65e6-0e84-4fa3-a596-7b35eb38fb2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-Z-J"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317068439","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317068439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a45b65e6-0e84-4fa3-a596-7b35eb38fb2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_U-L-H"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317078276","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317078276"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a45b65e6-0e84-4fa3-a596-7b35eb38fb2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_Y-U-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317083011","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317083011"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a45b65e6-0e84-4fa3-a596-7b35eb38fb2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_G-B-H"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317088324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317088324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a45b65e6-0e84-4fa3-a596-7b35eb38fb2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_O-H-N"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317104627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317104627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a45b65e6-0e84-4fa3-a596-7b35eb38fb2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_O-H-F"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317108916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317108916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a45b65e6-0e84-4fa3-a596-7b35eb38fb2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_F-H-D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317114729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317114729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" a45b65e6-0e84-4fa3-a596-7b35eb38fb2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_H_F-H-D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317127999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317127998"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 915369c9-3538-4062-95cd-1ab0271de3b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-2-11"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317209187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317209187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 915369c9-3538-4062-95cd-1ab0271de3b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-2-11"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317216859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317216858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 915369c9-3538-4062-95cd-1ab0271de3b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-2-11"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317228627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317228627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317229669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317229668"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317231008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317231007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAAMKA"," userResponse":" ANAAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317231869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317231869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317232797","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317232797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317233390","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317233390"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317234314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317234312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317237755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317237755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317238324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317238324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317239036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317239035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317239613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317239613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317239793","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317239793"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317241024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317241024"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317244691","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317244690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHUKURU"," userResponse":" ANASHUKURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317245181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317245181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317245986","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317245986"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317246965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317246964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOPITA"," userResponse":" ULIOPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317250312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317250311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317250882","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317250881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317251586","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317251586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317252161","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317252161"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317252335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317252335"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317253570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317253569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317257272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317257271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANATANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317258064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317258063"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317258786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317258786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317259886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317259885"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIZURI"," userResponse":" VIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317260477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317260477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317263749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317263749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317264330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317264329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317265061","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317265060"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317265688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317265688"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317265862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317265862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317267089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317267089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317271084","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317271083"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWASALIMU"," userResponse":" ANAWASALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317271779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317271779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317272382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317272381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317272632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317272632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317273636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317273636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABABU"," userResponse":" MABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317274288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317274288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317277795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317277794"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317278359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317278359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317279064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317279064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317279672","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317279671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317279859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317279859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317281083","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317281083"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317284484","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317284484"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOSHA"," userResponse":" ANAOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317284939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317284939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USO"," userResponse":" USO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317285523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317285522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317285786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317285786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317286630","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317286630"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" SABUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317286774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317286774"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317287448","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317287448"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" BLUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317290859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317290859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317291424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317291424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317292128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317292128"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317292702","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317292702"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317292877","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317292877"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317294114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317294113"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317297545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317297544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPIGA"," userResponse":" ANAPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317298424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317298424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" MSWAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317299036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317299036"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317299611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317299611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317299900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317299900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317300738","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317300737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" MSWAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317301410","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317301409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AINA"," userResponse":" AINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317301699","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317301698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317302644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317302644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LUGHANO"," userResponse":" LUGHANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317305981","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317305981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317306554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317306554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317307264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317307263"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317307863","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317307862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317308045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317308044"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317309289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317309288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317312547","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317312547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317312916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317312916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317313465","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317313465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317314336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317314336"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317317696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317317695"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317318265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317318264"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317318978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317318976"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317319554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317319554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317319730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317319730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317320962","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317320961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317324261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317324260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAVAA"," userResponse":" ANAVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317324912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317324911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317325036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317325036"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317325517","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317325517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317325880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317325880"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317326530","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317326529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317326687","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317326687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317327642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317327642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" MACHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317331048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317331046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317331656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317331655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317332369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317332369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317332968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317332967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317333156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317333155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317334381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317334380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317337688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317337688"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAVAA"," userResponse":" ANAVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317338481","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317338481"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317339095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317339095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKE"," userResponse":" VYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317339948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317339947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYEUSI"," userResponse":" VYEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317343469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317343468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317344085","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317344085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317344790","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317344790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317345375","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317345375"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317345549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317345549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317346797","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317346797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317350097","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317350097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anafika shuleni mapema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKA"," userResponse":" ANAFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317350787","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317350786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anafika shuleni mapema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317351953","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317351952"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anafika shuleni mapema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317355315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317355315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317355891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317355891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317356595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317356595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317357193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317357192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317357377","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317357377"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317358609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317358609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317362313","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317362313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAJIFUNZA"," userResponse":" ANAJIFUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317363148","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317363148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" MASOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317363341","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317363340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317364704","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317364704"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAYANSI"," userResponse":" SAYANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317365486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317365485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317366912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317366912"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJAMII"," userResponse":" KIJAMII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317367371","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317367370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317368252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317368252"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HESABU"," userResponse":" HESABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317371595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317371594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317372170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317372169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317372881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317372881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317373469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317373469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317373655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317373654"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317374892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317374891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317378221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317378220"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAIMBA"," userResponse":" ANAIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317378502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317378502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317379397","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317379397"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317381533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317381532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OTAMENHAIBUGA"," userResponse":" OTAMENHAIBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317382765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317382765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317383052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317383052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317383676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317383676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317383899","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317383899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317384547","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317384546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317387896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317387896"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317388488","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317388488"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317389212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317389211"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317389790","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317389790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317389972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317389971"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317391205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317391205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317393773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317393773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317393834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317393834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317401840","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317401840"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..25.off2.18__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317408818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317408817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" b0be8365-0884-47ff-b4d1-31a7d1f95354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317418368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317418368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317421652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317421652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317425477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317425477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317428556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317428556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317431648","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317431648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317434855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317434855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317437909","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317437908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317441014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317441014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317444176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317444175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317447744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317447743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317451321","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317451321"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317454756","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317454756"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317461512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317461512"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317465038","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317465037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317468135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317468134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317472484","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317472484"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317478387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317478387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317489723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317489722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317493027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317493027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317496002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317496001"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317499992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317499992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317502901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317502901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317505892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317505891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317508908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317508908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317512171","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317512170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317517925","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317517925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 82084314-a6f1-4cb3-a594-8540af086ff4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317528218","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317528218"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317528451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317528450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317528894","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317528893"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317529329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317529329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317529644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317529644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317530439","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317530439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317531035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317531035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317531281","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317531280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317532066","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317532066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317534834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317534834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317535810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317535810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317536245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317536245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317536433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317536432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317537030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317537029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317540131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317540131"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOA"," userResponse":" ILITOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317540761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317540761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317541521","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317541520"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317544569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317544569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317545245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317545244"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317546100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317546100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317546357","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317546357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317547117","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317547117"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317547979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317547979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317549071","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317549071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317550096","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317550095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKWENDA"," userResponse":" TUTAKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317551022","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317551021"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317552096","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317552095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317552525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317552525"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317553144","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317553144"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317553328","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317553328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317553964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317553964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317557192","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317557192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317558359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317558358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317559091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317559091"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317562422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317562422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESAFIRIA"," userResponse":" ANGESAFIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317563095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317563094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317563528","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317563528"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317564052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317564052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317564554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317564554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317564779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317564778"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317565483","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317565483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317568254","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317568253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317568837","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317568837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317569373","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317569373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317569832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317569832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317573049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317573049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317573812","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317573811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317574756","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317574756"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317576111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317576111"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVAA"," userResponse":" AMEVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317576765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317576765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317577152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317577152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317577685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317577684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317578774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317578774"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" ALIKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317579875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317579875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUAMSHA"," userResponse":" KUMUAMSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317583375","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317583375"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317583597","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317583596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317583992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317583992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317584514","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317584514"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317585715","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317585715"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" WALITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317586588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317586588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317587633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317587633"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317588278","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317588278"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317588551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317588551"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317589158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317589158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317592347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317592347"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISUBIRI"," userResponse":" WALISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317592705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317592705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317593175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317593174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317593757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317593757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317593958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317593958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317594557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317594556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317596861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317596860"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317597316","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317597316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317598524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317598524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUFIKA"," userResponse":" HAIKUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317601545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317601545"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317602209","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317602209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317603020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317603020"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317603494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317603494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317603959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317603958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317604528","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317604528"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317607942","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317607942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilalamika kwani basi ilichelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILALAMIKA"," userResponse":" WALILALAMIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317608461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317608461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilalamika kwani basi ilichelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317609062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317609062"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilalamika kwani basi ilichelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317610157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317610156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilalamika kwani basi ilichelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILICHELEWA"," userResponse":" ILICHELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317612502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317612502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi imetuacha?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317613800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317613799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi imetuacha?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMETUACHA"," userResponse":" IMETUACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317616708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317616708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317617779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317617779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317618053","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317618053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317619313","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317619313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIWASI"," userResponse":" WASIWASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317622358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317622358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatutaweza kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUTAWEZA"," userResponse":" HATUTAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317622987","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317622987"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatutaweza kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317623929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317623929"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatutaweza kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317626755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317626754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITAPATA"," userResponse":" SITAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317627096","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317627096"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317627636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317627636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317627720","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317627720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317628397","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317628397"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317629681","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317629680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAZA"," userResponse":" ALIWAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317633315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317633314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317633448","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317633448"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317633993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317633993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317634969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317634969"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATA"," userResponse":" WALIKATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317635786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317635786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317636591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317636591"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKARUDI"," userResponse":" WAKARUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317637437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317637436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317640172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317640172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317640786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317640786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317641761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317641761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" ALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317643245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317643245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAKATAA"," userResponse":" AKAKATAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317643988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317643988"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317646260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317646260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317646795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317646795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317648280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317648280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMTULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317649906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317649906"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TUTASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317650933","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317650933"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317654351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317654350"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla walisikia kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317655737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317655737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla walisikia kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISIKIA"," userResponse":" WALISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317656552","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317656552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla walisikia kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317659159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317659159"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaona vumbi hewani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAONA"," userResponse":" WAKAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317659820","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317659819"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaona vumbi hewani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VUMBI"," userResponse":" VUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317660573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317660573"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaona vumbi hewani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEWANI"," userResponse":" HEWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317662925","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317662925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ilikuwa inakuja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317663563","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317663563"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ilikuwa inakuja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317664431","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317664431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ilikuwa inakuja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAKUJA"," userResponse":" INAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317667814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317667814"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikuwa buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317668316","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317668315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikuwa buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317668974","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317668974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikuwa buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUWA"," userResponse":" HAIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317669406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317669406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikuwa buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317672595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317672595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUWA"," userResponse":" HAIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317673251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317673251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317675678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317675677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317676103","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317676103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317676890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317676890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317677837","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317677837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317678233","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317678232"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317678897","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317678897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317682397","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317682397"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliosubiri waliiangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOSUBIRI"," userResponse":" WALIOSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317684701","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317684701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliosubiri waliiangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIANGALIA"," userResponse":" WALIIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317688078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317688077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakuingia ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUINGIA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317688621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317688621"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakuingia ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317691978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317691977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317692953","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317692953"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITA"," userResponse":" ALIITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317696052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317696052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumechelewa sana leo alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMECHELEWA"," userResponse":" TUMECHELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317696524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317696524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumechelewa sana leo alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317697378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317697377"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumechelewa sana leo alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317698372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317698372"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumechelewa sana leo alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317701778","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317701777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317701943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317701943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317702324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317702324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317702824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317702824"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317703508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317703508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317703698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317703698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317704199","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317704198"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317704965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317704965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUINGIA"," userResponse":" KUINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317707400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317707400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317707889","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317707889"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317708610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317708610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317709591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317709591"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIA"," userResponse":" ALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317710162","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317710161"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317710226","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317710226"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317710807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317710807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317711158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317711157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317711653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317711653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317712389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317712388"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317715495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317715494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei aliangalia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317716307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317716307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei aliangalia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANGALIA"," userResponse":" ALIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317717514","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317717512"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei aliangalia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHANI"," userResponse":" DIRISHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317720359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317720358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317720822","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317720822"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317721486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317721486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317722188","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317722188"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317723057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317723057"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317723635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317723635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317723807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317723806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317724395","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317724395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317727394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317727394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317727968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317727968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317728718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317728718"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317730126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317730126"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" WALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317731196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317731196"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIFIKIA"," userResponse":" KUIFIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317731887","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317731886"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317734489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317734489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikuwa wamechelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317735359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317735358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikuwa wamechelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317736417","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317736417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikuwa wamechelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMECHELEWA"," userResponse":" WAMECHELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317738968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317738967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi iliondoka kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317740050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317740049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi iliondoka kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIONDOKA"," userResponse":" ILIONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317740582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317740581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi iliondoka kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317741483","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317741483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi iliondoka kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317744434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317744434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317744895","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317744894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317745413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317745412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317745679","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317745679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317746604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317746604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317749010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317749010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama yake Ebei aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317749484","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317749483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama yake Ebei aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317750119","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317750118"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama yake Ebei aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317750994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317750994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama yake Ebei aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317754281","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317754281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliharibika dereva alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIHARIBIKA"," userResponse":" ILIHARIBIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317755067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317755067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliharibika dereva alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317756152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317756151"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliharibika dereva alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIMJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317758754","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317758754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho itakuja aliongeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317759751","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317759750"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho itakuja aliongeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ITAKUJA"," userResponse":" ITAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317760994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317760994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho itakuja aliongeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONGEZA"," userResponse":" ALIONGEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317764038","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317764038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317765091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317765091"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUJALI"," userResponse":" HAKUJALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317765546","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317765546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317765671","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317765671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317766474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317766474"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317769221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317769220"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakujali ukubwa wa basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUJALI"," userResponse":" HAKUJALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317769935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317769935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakujali ukubwa wa basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUBWA"," userResponse":" UKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317770119","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317770119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakujali ukubwa wa basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317770874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317770874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakujali ukubwa wa basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317774631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317774631"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317775334","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317775334"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317775853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317775853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317776521","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317776520"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317777387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317777387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317778110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317778110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAKWENDA"," userResponse":" INAKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317778988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317778988"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317781559","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317781558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317781656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317781656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" de09b862-56e8-4ba8-85e5-62ea0fee959d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317792171","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317792171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 68e7b677-f695-4331-a0d3-48a98e0d8698"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" IMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317800049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317800048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 68e7b677-f695-4331-a0d3-48a98e0d8698"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317801634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317801633"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 68e7b677-f695-4331-a0d3-48a98e0d8698"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ILIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" ILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317805988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317805988"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 68e7b677-f695-4331-a0d3-48a98e0d8698"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ILIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317807554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317807554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 68e7b677-f695-4331-a0d3-48a98e0d8698"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" IMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317809126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317809126"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 68e7b677-f695-4331-a0d3-48a98e0d8698"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317809250","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317809250"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 68e7b677-f695-4331-a0d3-48a98e0d8698"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" IMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317821421","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317821421"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0acd9185-c707-4795-85bc-4d07c89a9075"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" IMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317825240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317825240"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0acd9185-c707-4795-85bc-4d07c89a9075"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317826813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317826813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0acd9185-c707-4795-85bc-4d07c89a9075"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ILIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" ILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317830508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317830507"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0acd9185-c707-4795-85bc-4d07c89a9075"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ILIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317832096","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317832096"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0acd9185-c707-4795-85bc-4d07c89a9075"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" INGIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" INGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317836394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317836394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0acd9185-c707-4795-85bc-4d07c89a9075"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" INGIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317837942","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317837942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0acd9185-c707-4795-85bc-4d07c89a9075"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" IMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317842322","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317842322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0acd9185-c707-4795-85bc-4d07c89a9075"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317844338","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317844338"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0acd9185-c707-4795-85bc-4d07c89a9075"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548317844627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548317844627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_105628"," gameId":" 0acd9185-c707-4795-85bc-4d07c89a9075"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}